A Guide to the Records of T. Marshall Hahn Jr, 1962-1974
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series VI, 1972-1973
  - Commission on Student Affairs #4, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 2677)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Studies, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2678)
  - Building Committee, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2679)
  - Catalog committee, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2680)
  - Commencement Committee, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2681)
  - Computer Committee, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2682)
  - Employee Benefits Committee, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2683)
  - Grievance Committee, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2684)
  - Honor Court Review Board, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2685)
  - Committee on International Programs, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2686)
  - Judical Committee, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2687)
  - Library Committee, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2688)
  - Committees - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2689)
  - Committee on Patents, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2690)
  - Radiation Safety Committee, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2691)
  - Scheduling and Registration Committee, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2692)
  - Scholarship & Student Aid Committee, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2693)
  - Student Health Coordinating Committee, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2694)
  - Traffic Committee, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2695)
  - Traffic Appeals Subcommittee, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2696)
  - University Committee on Student Records, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2697)
  - Committee to Study the University Honor System, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2698)
  - Committee on University Sanctioned Awards, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2699)
  - University Committee on Excellence in Teaching, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2700)
  - Commission on Research and Graduate Studies, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2701)
  - Completed Orders, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2702)
  - Consortium For Continuing Higher Education #1, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2703)
  - Consortium For Continuing Higher Education #2, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2704)
  - Consulting, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2705)
  - Cooperative Program, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2706)
  - Corps of Cadets, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2707)
  - Council on Presidents #1, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2708)
  - Council on Presidents #2, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2709)
  - Counseling Center, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2710)
  - Dairy Science, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2711)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2712)
  - Dean's - General, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2713)
  - Dedications, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2714)
  - Development - Bell, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2715)
  - Development - General, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2716)
  - Donaldson Brown Center, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2717)
  - Economics Department, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2718)
  - Editorial Projects For Education EPE Reports, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2719)
- Series VII, 1973-1974
  - Education, College of, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2720)
  - Electrical Engineering Department, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2721)
  - Engineering and Building, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2722)
  - Engineering, College of, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2723)
  - Engineering Science and Mechanics Department, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2724)
  - English Department, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2725)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2726)
  - Entomology Department, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2727)
  - Esso Educational Foundation, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2728)
  - Environmental Studies, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2729)
  - Exchange Visitor Program DSP-66, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2730)
  - Executive Bulletins, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2731)
  - Extension Division - Skelton, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2732)
  - Extension - General, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2733)
  - Extension - State Technical Service, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2734)
  - Faculty and Christmas List (Reception), 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2735)
  - Faculty Promotions, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2736)
  - Faculty Senate #1, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2737)
  - Faculty Senate #2, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2738)
  - Faculty Senate #3, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2739)
  - Ferrum Junior College, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2740)
  - Field House, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2741)
  - Football #1, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2742)
  - Football #2, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2743)
  - Food Science and Technology Department, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2744)
  - Founder's Day, April 19, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2745)
  - Foreign Languages, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2746)
  - Forestry and Wildlife, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2747)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2748)
  - Geological Sciences Department, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2749)
  - Georgia - Pacific Corporation, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2750)
  - Glee Club, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2751)
  - Governor of Virginia (Earl J. Shiflet, Secretary of Education), 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2752)
  - Governor of Virginia #1, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2753)
  - Governor of Virginia #2, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2754)
  - Governor's Ad Hoc Committee to Review Va Area Development Act, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2755)
  - Governor's Day, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2756)
  - Graduate School, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2757)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2758)
  - Dr Hahn - Biographical Sketches and Photographs, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2759)
  - Dr Hahn - Personal #1, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2760)
  - Dr Hahn - Personal #2, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2761)
  - Dr Hahn - Personal #3, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2762)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2763)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2764)
  - Highway Department, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2765)
  - History Department, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2766)
  - Homecoming, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2767)
  - Home Economics, College of, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2768)
  - Horticulture Department, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2769)
  - Industrial Engineering Department, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2770)
  - Information Services #1, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2771)
  - Information Services #2, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2772)
  - Institutional Research #1, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2773)
  - Institutional Research #2, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2774)
  - Invitations - Miscellaneous #1, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2775)
  - Invitations - Miscellaneous #2, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2776)
  - Invitations - Inaugurations, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2777)
  - Johnston, J Ambler, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2778)
  - K - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2779)
  - The Lane Company, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2780)
  - Learning Resources Center, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2781)
  - Legislators - U. S. Congress #1, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2782)
  - Legislators - U. S. Congress #2, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2783)
  - Legislators - General Assembly #1, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2784)
  - Legislators - General Assembly #2, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2785)
  - General Assembly Commission on Higher Education (Correspondence), 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2786)
  - General Assembly Commission on Higher Education (Rebuttal to Consultants Report), October 2, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2787)
  - General Assembly Commission on Higher Education (Shaner Report), 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2788)
  - Library, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2789)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2790)
  - Mathematics Department, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2791)
  - Mechanical Engineering Department, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2792)
  - Minerals Engineering, Division of, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2793)
  - Miscellaneous #1, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2794)
  - Miscellaneous #2, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2795)
  - Miscellaneous #3, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2796)
  - Multi-purpose Agricultural Research Station #1, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2797)
  - National Science Foundation #1, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2798)
  - National Science Foundation #2, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2799)
  - Norfolk Area Medical Center Authority, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2800)
  - O - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2801)
  - Oak Ridge Association Universities ORAU, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2802)
  - P - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2803)
  - Performing Arts and Communications, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2804)
  - Personnel - A. T. Butt, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2805)
  - Personnel - Richmond, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2806)
  - Philippines, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2807)
  - Philosophy and Religion Department, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2808)
  - Physics Department, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2809)
  - Physical Education Department, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2810)
  - Physical Plant Planning, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2811)
  - Placement, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2812)
  - Political Science Department, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2813)
  - Psychology Department, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2814)
  - R - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2815)
  - Purchasing Department, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 2816)
  - Reception #1, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2817)
  - Reception #2, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2818)
  - Registrar, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2819)
  - Recommendations, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2820)
  - Research Division #1, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2821)
  - Research Division #2, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2822)
  - Reston, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2823)
  - Retirement, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2824)
  - Reynolds Homestead Research Center, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2825)
  - Ross, David L., 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2826)
  - ROTC, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2827)
  - Ryland, Walter H. #1, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2828)
  - S - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2829)
  - Salaries, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2830)
  - Salvation Army #1, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2831)
  - Salvation Army #2, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2832)
  - Savage, Lon K., 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2833)
  - Scholarships and Grants #1, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2834)
  - Scholarships and Grants #2, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2835)
  - Scholarships and Grants #3, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2836)
  - Security Division, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2837)
  - Smithfield Plantation, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2838)
  - Southern Association of Colleges And Schools, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2839)
  - Southern Regional Education Board SREB #1, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2840)
  - Southern Regional Education Board SREB #2, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2841)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2842)
  - Speech Material, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2843)
  - Speeches, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2844)
  - Sporn Awards, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2845)
  - Staff Meeting #1, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2846)
  - Staff Meeting #2, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2847)
  - State Council on Higher Education #1, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2848)
  - State Council on Higher Education #2, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2849)
  - State Council on Higher Education #3, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2850)
  - State Council on Higher Education #4, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2851)
  - State Council on Higher Education #5, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2852)
  - State Council on Higher Education #6, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2853)
  - Statistics Department, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2854)
  - Student Government Association #1, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2855)
  - Student Housing #1, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2856)
  - Student Housing #2, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2857)
  - Student Letters - Others #1, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2858)
  - Student Letters - Others #2, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2859)
  - Student Letters - To and From #1, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2860)
  - Student Affairs - Payne, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2861)
  - Student Organizations, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2862)
  - Student Publications Board, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2863)
  - Student Residence Programs - Hill, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2864)
  - Student Services, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2865)
  - Student Union, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2866)
  - Summer School Programs, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2867)
  - Subscriptions, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2868)
  - T - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2869)
  - Task Force For Innovative Approaches to Instruction #1, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2870)
  - Task Force For Innovative Approaches to Instruction #2, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2871)
  - University Council #1, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2872)
  - University Council #2, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2873)
  - University Council #3, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2874)
  - University Council #4, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2875)
  - University Council #5, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2876)
  - University Professors, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2877)
  - University Services and Auxiliary Enterprises, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2878)
  - V - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2879)
  - Veterinary Science Department, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2880)
  - Proposed College of Veterinary Medicine In Virginia #1, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2881)
  - Proposed College of Veterinary Medicine In Virginia #2, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2882)
  - Vice President - Admissions #1, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2883)
  - Executive Vice President #1, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2884)
  - Executive Vice President #2, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2885)
  - Vice President - Academic Affairs #1, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2886)
  - Vice President - Academic Affairs #2, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2887)
  - Vice President - Finance #1, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2888)
  - Vice President - Student Affairs #1, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2889)
  - Vice President - Student Affairs #2, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2890)
  - Vice President - Student Affairs #3, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2891)
  - Vice President - Student Affairs #4, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2892)
  - Vice President - Student Affairs #5, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2893)
  - Virginia Academy of Science, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2894)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2895)
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture and Commerce #1, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2896)
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture and Commerce #2, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2897)
  - Virginia Tech Athletic Association #1, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2898)
  - Virginia Tech Athletic Association #2, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2899)
  - Virginia Tech Student Aid Association, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2900)
  - Virginia Truck Experimental Station, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2901)
  - VPI Educational Foundation, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2902)
  - VPI Educational Foundation -President's Fund, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2903)
  - Visiting Scholars Program, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2904)
  - W - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2905)
  - Water Resources Research Center, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2906)
  - Western Region Consortium for Continuing Higher Education, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2907)
  - Wine Awards, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2908)
  - YMCA, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 2909)
  - A - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 2910)
  - AAUP, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 2911)
  - AAUW, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 2912)
  - Accounting - Burruss Hall, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 2913)
  - Accounting Department, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 2914)
  - Appendix Materials for Report of the Ad Hoc University Calender Committee, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 2915)
  - Additional Documents Reviewed by the Ad Hoc University Calendar Committee, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 2916)
  - Admissions and Records #1, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 2917)
  - Admissions and Records #2, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 2918)
  - Administrators Conference, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 2919)
  - Aerospace Engineering, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 2920)
  - Agricultural Engineering Department, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 2921)
  - Agriculture and Life Sciences, College of #1, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2922)
  - Agronomy Department, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2923)
  - Aircraft, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2924)
  - Alumni Contributions (A-G), 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2925)
  - Alumni Contributions (H-L), 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2926)
  - Alumni Contributions (M-Q), 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2927)
  - Alumni contributions (R-Z), 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2928)
  - Alumni Association - General #1, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2929)
  - Alumni Association - General #2, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2930)
  - Alumni Distinguished Professor, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2931)
  - Alumni Association - President, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2932)
  - Alumni Congratulatory letters, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2933)
  - American Cancer Society, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2934)
  - American Council on Education, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2935)
  - Anaerobe Laboratory, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2936)
  - Animal Industry Day, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2937)
  - Animal Science Department, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2938)
  - Applications for Positions, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2939)
  - Architecture, College of, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2940)
  - Arts and Sciences, College of, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2941)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2942)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2943)
  - Southern Association of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2944)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2945)
  - Attorney General of Va., 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2946)
  - B - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2947)
  - Basketball, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2948)
  - Bequests, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2949)
  - Biochemistry and Nutrition Department, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2950)
  - Biology Department, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2951)
  - Blacksburg, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2952)
  - Board of Visitors #1, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2953)
  - Board of Visitors #2, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2954)
  - Board of Visitors - Correspondence #1, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2955)
  - Board of Visitors - Correspondence #2, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2956)
  - Board of Visitors - Correspondence #3, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2957)
  - Board of Visitors - Minutes #1, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2958)
  - Board of Visitors - Minutes #2, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2959)
  - Board of Visitors - Brinkley, Parke C., 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2960)
  - Board of Visitors - Casto, H., 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2961)
  - Board of Visitors - Clement, G. F., 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2962)
  - Board of Visitors - Cutchins, C. A., 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2963)
  - Board of Visitors - Faircloth, J. T. Jr., 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2964)
  - Board of Visitors - Givens, J. E., 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2965)
  - Board of Visitors - Goodykoontz, R. A., 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2966)
  - Board of Visitors - Kraft, C. C. Jr., 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2967)
  - Board of Visitors - Lane, Mrs E. N., 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2968)
  - Board of Visitors - Pamplin, R. B., 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2969)
  - Board of Visitors - Robinson, Mrs J Kenneth, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2970)
  - Board of Visitors - Rowe, C. Eugene, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2971)
  - Board of Visitors - Russell, R. E., 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2972)
  - Board of Visitors - Smith, R. R., 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2973)
  - Board of Visitors - Whitehurst, J. L., 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2974)
  - Board of Visitors - Dr James F. Tucker, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2975)
  - Budget Division - McCutcheson, J. R. Jr, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2976)
  - Budget Matters, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2977)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2978)
  - Business Manager, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2979)
  - Business, College of, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2980)
  - Business Administration Department, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2981)
  - Commission on Faculty Affairs, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2982)
  - Commission on Research and Graduate Studies, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2983)
  - Commission on Student Affairs #1, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2984)
  - Commission on Student Affairs #2, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2985)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Studies, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 2986)
  - Building Committee, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 2987)
  - Catalogue Committee, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 2988)
  - Committee on Copyrights, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 2989)
  - Computer Committee, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 2990)
  - Employee Benefits Committee, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 2991)
  - Grievance Committee, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 2992)
  - Honor Court Review Board Committee, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 2993)
  - Committee on International Programs, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 2994)
  - Judicial Committee, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 2995)
  - Library Committee, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 2996)
  - Committees - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 2997)
  - Committee on Patents, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 2998)
  - Radiation Safety Committee, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 2999)
  - Scheduling and Registration Committee, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3000)
  - Scholarships and Student Aid Committee, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3001)
  - Traffic Committee, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3002)
  - Traffic Appeals Subcommittee, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3003)
  - Commencement Committee, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3004)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3005)
  - Committee to Study the University Honor System, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3006)
  - University Committee for Excellence in Teaching, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3007)
  - Committee on University Sanctioned Awards, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3008)
  - C - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3009)
  - Capital Outlay Requests, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3010)
  - Central Va Consortium, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3011)
  - Chemical Engineering, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3012)
  - Chemistry Department, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3013)
  - Chronicle of Higher Education, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3014)
  - Cincinnati Award, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3015)
  - Cincinnati Inc., 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3016)
  - Civil Engineering Department, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3017)
  - Civil Rights (Tallaferro, Dyson, Schotta, et al.) Correspondence #1, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3018)
  - Civil Rights (Tallaferro, Dyson, Schotta, et al.) Correspondence #2, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3019)
  - Civil Rights (Tallaferro, Dyson, Schotta, et al.) Correspondence #3, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3020)
  - Civil Rights (Title IX, Education Amendments Acts - NCAA New), 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3021)
  - Civil Rights - Correspondence Between New and Governor, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3022)
  - Civil Rights (Patricia Bond, Et Al Class Action Suit), 1974 (Box 88, Folder 3023)
  - Commencement File, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3024)
  - Commandant of Cadet, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3025)
  - Commonwealth Conference on Higher Education, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3026)
  - Editorial Projects For Ed. EPE Reports, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3027)
  - Completed Orders #1, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3028)
  - Completed Orders #2, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3029)
  - Completed Orders #3, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3030)
  - Computer Science Department, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3031)
  - Computing Center, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3032)
  - Community Colleges, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3033)
  - Consortium For Continuing Higher Education in Northern Virginia #1, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3034)
  - Consortium For Continuing Higher Education in Northern Virginia #2, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3035)
  - Consulting, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3036)
  - Cooperative Program, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3037)
  - Corps of Cadets, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3038)
  - Council of Presidents #1, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3039)
  - Council of Presidents #2, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3040)
  - Counseling Center, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3041)
  - D - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3042)
  - Dairy Science, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3043)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3044)
  - Deans - General, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3045)
  - Dedications, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3046)
  - Development - Bell, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3047)
  - Development - General, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3048)
  - Donaldson Brown Center, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3049)
  - Economics Department, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3050)
  - EDUCOM, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3051)
  - Engineering and Building, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3052)
  - Education, College of, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3053)
  - Engineering, College of, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3054)
  - Electrical Engineering Department, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3055)
  - English Department, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3056)
  - Enrollment Studies, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3057)
  - Exxon Education Foundation, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3058)
  - Executive Bulletins, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3059)
  - Extension General, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3060)
  - Extension Division - Skelton, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3061)
  - Extension - State Technical Services, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3062)
  - Faculty Positions, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3063)
  - Faculty Promotions, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3064)
  - Faculty Senate #1, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3065)
  - Faculty Senate #2, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3066)
  - Ferrum Junior College, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3067)
  - Food Science and Technology Department, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3068)
  - Ford Foundation, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3069)
  - Forestry and Wildlife, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3070)
  - Football #1, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3071)
  - Football #2, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3072)
  - Football Guest List, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3073)
  - Founder's Day, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3074)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3075)